[
    {
       "question":"Which poison did Bruno eat?",
       "choice1":"Barium Chloride",
       "choice2": "Barium Carbonate",
       "choice3": "Barium Sulphide",
       "choice4": "Barium bi-carbonate",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"What is the main food of sloth bears ?",
       "choice1":"Apple",
       "choice2":"Rice",
       "choice3":"Milk",
       "choice4":"Termites",
       "answer": 4
   },
   {
       "question":"What was put around the neck of the baby sloth bear ?",
       "choice1":"A piece of scarf",
       "choice2": "A belt",
       "choice3": "A coloured ribbon",
       "choice4": "A black rope",
       "answer": 3
   
   },
   {
       "question":"After eating some poison what happened to Bruno?",
       "choice1":"Died",
       "choice2":"Got fainted",
       "choice3":"Got paralysed",
       "choice4":"Poison didn't affected it",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"The lesson 'Kathmandu' has been written by - ",
       "choice1":"Isaac Asimov",
       "choice2": "A. P. J. Abdul Kalam",
       "choice3": "Vikram Seth",
       "choice4": "Doughlas James",
       "answer": 3
   
   },
   {
       "question":"A sign proclaimes 'Entrance for the Hindus only' at -",
       "choice1":"Baudhnath Temple",
       "choice2":"Pashupatinath Temple",
       "choice3":"Baidyanath Temple",
       "choice4":"Lotus Temple",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"'Pashupatinath Temple' is situated in - ",
       "choice1":"India",
       "choice2": "Sikkim",
       "choice3": "Nepal",
       "choice4": "Tibet",
       "answer": 3
   
   },
   {
       "question":" 'Pashupatinath temple' is situated on the bank of river -",
       "choice1":"Bagmati",
       "choice2":"Saraswati",
       "choice3":"Ganga",
       "choice4":"Gandhak",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"The Baudhnath Stupa is situated in-",
       "choice1":"Kathmandu",
       "choice2": "Janakpur",
       "choice3": "Birpur",
       "choice4": "None of these",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"'The Baudhnath Stupa' is a sacred place for:",
       "choice1":"The Hindus",
       "choice2":"The Buddhists",
       "choice3":"The Jains",
       "choice4":"The Sikhs",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"Kathmandu is the capital of -",
       "choice1":"Burma",
       "choice2": "Bangladesh",
       "choice3": "Nepal",
       "choice4": "China",
       "answer": 3
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Who jumped onto a Shivaling at Pashupatinath temple ?",
       "choice1":"A dog",
       "choice2":"A cat",
       "choice3":"A monkey",
       "choice4":"A rat",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Who had written 'If I Were You'?",
       "choice1":"Vikram Seth",
       "choice2": "Douglas James",
       "choice3": "James Kirikup",
       "choice4": "Kenneth Anderson",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"What kind of glasses is Gerrard wearing ?",
       "choice1":"Round",
       "choice2":"Flat",
       "choice3":"Black",
       "choice4":"Horn-rimmed",
       "answer": 4
   },
   {
       "question":"An intruder is - ",
       "choice1":"a criminal",
       "choice2": "a professor",
       "choice3": "an stranger",
       "choice4": "a friend ",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"'If I were you' is a story of -",
       "choice1":"a beggar",
       "choice2":"a lawyer",
       "choice3":"an intruder",
       "choice4":"a magician",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Who was Gerrad ?",
       "choice1":"A playwright",
       "choice2": "A poet",
       "choice3": "A musician",
       "choice4": "A magician",
       "answer": 4
   
   },
   {
       "question":"The Christian's name of Gerrad was -",
       "choice1":"Isaac Newton",
       "choice2":"Harris",
       "choice3":"Vincent Charles",
       "choice4":"Jerome",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Who is the poet of the poem 'The Road Not Taken'?",
       "choice1":"William Butler Yeats",
       "choice2": "Robert Frost",
       "choice3": "Subramania Bharati",
       "choice4": "Edward Lear",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"What do the 'two roads' symbolise in the poem 'The Road Not Taken'?",
       "choice1":"two types of garments",
       "choice2":"two ways of life",
       "choice3":"two postures of reading",
       "choice4":"two ways of writing",
       "answer": 2
   }
   
   
   
   
   ]